- Morning.
- Morning. What's up?
(Leonard:)Nothing. We just pulled an all-nighter
trying to fix a Zero-Gravity pasta maker.
- I'm gonna make a coffee run. Want any?
- No. I have coffee.
(Stuart:)Great,
so how'd it go with Stuart last night?
I really don't wanna talk about it.
(Leonard:)Yeah. Right. Sure.
But, you know, the thing is,
before you guys went out...
- ...I spoke to him and I...
- I said I don't wanna talk about it.
- Okay, I kind of feel res...
- Look, Leonard.
What goes on is none of your business.
So just leave it alone, okay?
(Raj:)If you really want to clean up your karma,
go get my freaking latte.
(Howard:)Hang on, I think I've got this.
(Howard:)Help me see if we can wedge
this piece of PVC behind the support rod.
You're overestimating the strength
of the substructure you're building.